Guide to the Tyree Scott Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- NORTHWEST LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE (LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE) RECORDS, 1961-2005; SERIES 10 (Box-folder 16/32-45/15)
  - Case Files and Legal Papers, 1961-1995; Subseries C (Box-folder 18/33-45/15)
    - Women in Trades, et. al. v. John D. Spellman - Interrogatories, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/41)
    - Women in Trades, et. al. v. John D. Spellman - Plaintiff's Interrogatory Answer Materials, circa 1976 (Box-folder 40/42)
    - Women in Trades, et. al. v. John D. Spellman - Spellman Mootness Question, Undated (Box-folder 40/43)
    - Women in Trades, et. al. v. John D. Spellman - Summary Judgment & Mandamus Research, 1976 (Box-folder 40/44)
    - Women in Trades, et. al. v. John D. Spellman - Spellman Exhibits, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 40/45)
    - Women in Trades, et. al. v. John D. Spellman - Spellman Extra Pleadings, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 40/46)
    - Right to Work, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 40/47)
    - Calmecac (only copy of final report), circa 1970s (Box-folder 40/48)
    - Jacque Agtuca et. al. v. Tetsuden Kashma et. al, 1976 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Green Giant Company 7/78, 1978 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - United Farm Workers (UFW) / Immigration & Naturalization Service 8/78, 1978 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - Local 86 v. Associated General Contractors of America Inc. - Correspondence and Court Documents, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - Guadalupe "Lupe" Gamboa, 1977 (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Catholic Charities, circa 1970s (Box-folder 41/6)
    - Guillermo Nicacio v. A. Ludlow Kramer, et ux. - Interrogatory, 1975 (Box-folder 41/7)
    - Guillermo Nicacio v. A. Ludlow Kramer, et ux. - Plaintiff's First Proposed Pre-Trial Conference order, including all but exhibit N, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 41/8)
    - Domingo, Nemesio (v. City of Seattle) - Appeal February 12, 1975 Arrest (Box-folder 41/9)
    - Williams, Willie (v. City of Seattle) - February 13, 1975 Arrest (Box-folder 41/10)
    - Thomas, Robert (v. City of Seattle) - February 13, 1975 Arrest (Box-folder 41/11)
    - Thomas, Bobby Joe (v. City of Seattle) - February 12, 1975 Arrest (Box-folder 41/12)
    - John Yates Apprenticeship Termination, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 41/13)
    - Debra Lyles Apprenticeship Termination, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 41/14)
    - LeRoy Pines v. Republic Freight - Pleadings I, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 41/15)
    - Escobar, Jesus Property Damage 7/77, 1977 (Box-folder 41/16)
    - Escobar II - Adoption UFW 12/77, 1978 (Box-folder 41/17)
    - 1976 Pilipino People's Far West Convention (Box-folder 41/18)
    - Vasquez, Ramiro NFW 9176 Industrial Insurance, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 41/19)
    - Motion to Compel Green Giant - Evergreen Legal Services, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 41/20)
    - LSC Quarterly Report - National Employment Law Project, 1978 (Box-folder 41/21)
    - Villanueva, Enedelia "Lela" 3/76 School Suspension, 1976 (Box-folder 41/22)
    - Garza, Adam UFW 3/77 Property Damage, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 41/23)
    - Adam Garza Pleading File, 1978 (Box-folder 41/24)
    - Eric Franklin UPS 1/78, 1977 (Box-folder 41/25)
    - Holmes Electric, 1978 (Box-folder 41/26)
    - Octave Jules / Local 302 Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC) Charge, 1978 (Box-folder 41/27)
    - Campos, John UFW 9176 Industrial Insurance, 1976 (Box-folder 41/28)
    - Jose Angel Castro UFW, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 41/29)
    - UPS 1/78, 1977 (Box-folder 41/30)
    - Phil Imahara UPS 1/78, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 41/31)
    - Antonio Arteaga UFW, 1978 (Box-folder 41/32)
    - Corona, Jose UFW 3/77, 1977 (Box-folder 41/33)
    - Department of Labor & Industries Investigation, 1977 (Box-folder 41/34)
    - Gamache - Sex Discrimination, Organizing, 1978 (Box-folder 41/35)
    - CETA Funding 9/77, 1977 (Box-folder 41/36)
    - Lewis & Clark Conference 4/1/78 - Representing Minorities in the Legal System, 1978 (Box-folder 41/37)
    - Housing, 1978 (Box-folder 41/38)
    - Voting Requirements for Yakima County, Undated (Box-folder 41/39)
    - Organizing Information - UFW, 1978 (Box-folder 41/40)
    - Mt. Arbor Nurseries, Inc. 8/78, 1978 (Box-folder 41/41)
    - Gonzalo Silva-Lopez UFW 12/77, 1978 (Box-folder 41/42)
    - Gonzalo Silva Bar Complaint, 1978 (Box-folder 41/43)
    - Barrienties, Evangelina Injury Claim UFW, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 41/44)
    - Jose Spindola UFW 11/78, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 41/45)
    - Lupe Flores - Gamache 6/78, 1978 (Box-folder 41/46)
    - Margarita Gonzalez, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 41/47)
    - Willie Tyler v. Port of Seattle, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 41/48)
    - Lee, Lathan - Plumbers Apprentice Rates, 1977 (Box-folder 41/49)
    - Delgado, Jose 1/6/76, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 41/50)
    - Juan Cantu-Chapa Gamache/DWI 7/78, 1978 (Box-folder 41/51)
    - Rod Mamon - IBM Charges 9/77, 1977 (Box-folder 41/52)
    - Dorothy Chodkiewicz - Housing Discrimination 9/78, 1978 (Box-folder 41/53)
    - Garcia, Grasiela UFW Service Case, 1976 (Box-folder 41/54)
    - Gonzalez, Maria UFW 2/2/76, 1976 (Box-folder 41/55)
    - Cardenas, Donaciano, 1978 (Box-folder 41/56)
    - Rodrigo L. Barron, et. al. v. Seattle Community College, 1978 (Box-folder 41/57)
    - 6/77 Idaho Trip, Undated (Box-folder 41/58)
    - Sabina Iracheta UFW 2/78 - Vehicle Purchase Agreement, 1976 (Box-folder 41/59)
    - Francisco Lopez-Tavera UFW Workmen's Comp. 12/76, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 41/60)
    - Jessie Mapelli - Vehicular Accident, 1975 (Box-folder 41/61)
    - Leo Macias UFW 3/78 - Disorderly Conduct, 1978 (Box-folder 41/62)
    - NEFCO - Recall/Vacancy Research 12/76, Undated (Box-folder 41/63)
    - Perales, Francisco - Child Support, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 41/64)
    - Reyes, Yolanda UFW Birth Certificate, 1976 (Box-folder 41/65)
    - Johnson et al. v. Local 32 EEOC Charges & Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 41/66)
    - Leroy Pines v. Republic Freight, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 41/67)
    - Local 37 Elections, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 41/68)
    - Rivera, Ramon II, 1976 (Box-folder 41/69)
    - NEFCO - Rule 34 Computer Data Discovery Research, Undated (Box-folder 41/70)
    - Randy Hicks - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Transcript (1 of 2), 1977 (Box-folder 41/71)
    - Randy Hicks - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Transcript (2 of 2), 1977 (Box-folder 41/72)
    - Sanchez v. Compact City, Inc. Trial Notes and Exhibits, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 41/73)
    - United Farm Workers (UFW) v. Alexander, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 41/74)
    - Employee Retirement Income Security Act (ERISA) Consent Decree Petition, 1974 (Box-folder 41/75)
    - Evans v. Local 46, 1977 (Box-folder 41/76)
    - United Construction Workers Association (UCWA) v. Local 301 (MJG File), 1977 (Box-folder 41/77)
    - Sanchez v. Compact City, Inc. L.R Gere Deposition 3/19/79, 1976 (Box-folder 42/1)
    - James Thomas Disability, 1979 (Box-folder 42/2)
    - James Thomas v. Cental Pontiac, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 42/3)
    - Sanchez v. Gere - Pleadings, 1979 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - Sanchez v. Compact City - Documents Produced by Defendant, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - Sanchez v. Compact City - Misc. Documents, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - Sanchez v. Compact City - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - Affirmative Action for Women in Construction, 1977 (Box-folder 42/8)
    - Delester Walton (Edder, Inc.), 1977 (Box-folder 42/9)
    - Linda Davis v. United Parcel Service, 1978 (Box-folder 42/10)
    - Kenworth - Freedom of Information Act, 1977 (Box-folder 42/11)
    - Kenworth Truck Company - Blank Application for Employment, 1978 (Box-folder 42/12)
    - in re Arcia & United Parcel Service - NLRB Transcript, File 1 of 3, 1978 (Box-folder 42/13)
    - in re Arcia & United Parcel Service - NLRB Transcript, File 2 of 3, 1978 (Box-folder 42/14)
    - in re Arcia & United Parcel Service - NLRB Transcript, File 3 of 3, 1978 (Box-folder 42/15)
    - James Thomas v. Cental Pontiac, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 42/16)
    - Southwest LELO Proposal, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 42/17)
    - Newman v. Communication Workers - Amicus Brief & Other Materials, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 42/18)
    - Fundraising, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 42/19)
    - United Parcel Service v. National Labor Relations Board - Pleadings, 1978 (Box-folder 42/20)
    - King County Young Lawyers - Legal Problems of Elderly, 1979 (Box-folder 42/21)
    - Unemployment Clinic, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 42/22)
    - John Dickensheets - Pension, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 42/23)
    - Eric Franklin & United Parcel Service (NLRB), 1978 (Box-folder 42/24)
    - Emily Luna v. United Parcel Service, 1979 (Box-folder 42/25)
    - Michael Powell v. Peoples Bank, 1978 (Box-folder 42/26)
    - Direct Mail Solicitation, 1978 (Box-folder 42/27)
    - University of Oregon National Lawyers Guild Conference, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 42/28)
    - NEFCO, B.N., 6 Local 7 Government Contracts & Freedom of Information Act Requests, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 42/29)
    - Black Sheet Metal Workers Association - Articles of Incorporation & Bylaws, 1972 (Box-folder 42/30)
    - Lester Powell Jr. v. Holert Electric Inc., 1977-1979 (Box-folder 42/31)
    - Hasagowa & Kerrigan v. United Parcel Service - EEOC Charges, 1978 (Box-folder 42/32)
    - Southwest LELO Articles of Incorporation, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 42/33)
    - Tyree Scott, 1978 (Box-folder 42/34)
    - Donna Tuffree v. Teamsters 252, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 42/35)
    - Cordell Johnson - Workman's Compensation, 1978 (Box-folder 42/36)
    - Pensions - Electrical Workers, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 42/37)
    - Pensions - Plumbers & Pipefitters, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 42/38)
    - United Parcel Service Unit Work Problem, 1978 (Box-folder 42/39)
    - Don Stevens & Allied Sheet Metal - EEOC Charges, 1978 (Box-folder 42/40)
    - Lionel Hampton v. Local 32, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 42/41)
    - Intermittent City Employees, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 42/42)
    - Herman Lanier v. University of Washington, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 42/43)
    - State Credit Association v. Johnson, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 42/44)
    - Leonard Thomas & Burke Electric, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 42/45)
    - Communications Workers - Women's Caucus, 1977 (Box-folder 42/46)
    - Juan Antonia Rodriguez, 1978 (Box-folder 42/47)
    - Angel Alvizo, 1977 (Box-folder 42/48)
    - James Thomas - Disability, Social Security, 1978 (Box-folder 42/49)
    - Larry Arcia - United Parcel Service, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 42/50)
    - Hicks v. Local 174 (NLRB), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 42/51)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo - Labeling, Receipts, Packing, Invoices (Reviewed and Not Used), File 1 of 6, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 42/52)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo - Labeling, Receipts, Packing, Invoices (Reviewed and Not Used), File 2 of 6, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 42/53)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo - Labeling, Receipts, Packing, Invoices (Reviewed and Not Used), File 3 of 6, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo - Labeling, Receipts, Packing, Invoices (Reviewed and Not Used), File 4 of 6, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 43/2)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo - Labeling, Receipts, Packing, Invoices (Reviewed and Not Used), File 5 of 6, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo - Labeling, Receipts, Packing, Invoices (Reviewed and Not Used), File 6 of 6, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced (To Be Filed - Not Used), 1975 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced (Daily Time Slips), 1971 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo Packing Company Longshore Sheets, 1972 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo Packing Company Longshore Sheets, 1973 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced, 1974 (Box-folder 43/9)
    - Partnership Records of NEFCO & Whitney, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 43/10)
    - Receipts for Chatham Cannery (NEFCO), 1977 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced (Daily Time Slips), 1974 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo Ledgers, Receipts, Correspondence, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo Statistics (Interrogatories, Job Descriptions), circa 1970s (Box-folder 43/14)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Second Motion to Dismiss - Employee Tabulations, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - NEFCO Laundry Receipts (Box-folder 43/16)
    - Frank Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Inc. et. al. Deposition of Shirley Smith, 1981 (Box-folder 43/17)
    - Race Discrimination Charts and Notice to Class Flyer, Undated (Box-folder 43/18)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced (Food 1974) - Inter alia records with race notations and invoices with race notations (Box-folder 43/19)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced - Miscellaneous, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 43/20)
    - NEFCO Documentation - Log of Occupational Injuries and Illnesses, Budgets, Memorandum Regarding Employees, Receipts, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 43/21)
    - NEFCO Documentation - Receipts, Bareboat Charter Agreement, Accounting, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 43/22)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced (Food 1975) (Box-folder 43/23)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced (Food 1972) Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 43/24)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced (Food 1972) Part 2 of 2 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo - Miscellaneous Exhibits - Castro Testimony, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced - Miscellaneous, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced - Miscellaneous Part 1 of 3, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced - Miscellaneous Part 2 of 3, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced - Miscellaneous Part 3 of 3, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 44/6)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo - Miscellaneous Documents, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 44/7)
    - NEFCO Documentation - Alaska Airlines, Ketchikan, 1975 (Box-folder 44/8)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced (Food 1975) (Box-folder 44/9)
    - NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced - Miscellaneous including Correspondence, 1973 Annual Report, Stock Subscription, Meeting Minutes, Health and Safety, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 44/10)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Documents Produced - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box-folder 44/11)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Photographs, Undated (Box-folder 44/12)
    - Operational Check Balancing Log, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 44/13)
    - Beth Brunton - 1978 Work Study, 1977 (Box-folder 44/14)
    - Employment Discrimination Work, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 44/15)
    - Ercardo Lopez - 1979 Work Study, 1989 (Box-folder 44/16)
    - Stella Morris - Office Worker (hand written resume), Circa 1970's (Box-folder 44/17)
    - 1974 Budget and Expenses - LELO (Box-folder 44/18)
    - Frank B Hall and Company - Malpractice Insurance, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 44/19)
    - Personnel Correspondence II, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 44/20)
    - LELO - Telephone, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 44/21)
    - LELO - Travel Expenses, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 44/22)
    - Xerox Billings to others doing LELO counter, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 44/23)
    - Old LELO Funding Proposals, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 44/24)
    - Publication Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 44/25)
    - LELO Duplicate Articles, By-Laws, Etc., 1973-1974 (Box-folder 44/26)
    - Robert Green, 1977 (Box-folder 44/27)
    - LELO Name - Bar Application, Undated (Box-folder 44/28)
    - Nemvalts, Janet K. Resume, 1979 (Box-folder 44/29)
    - Law Student Applicants, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 44/30)
    - Susan Helf Work Study Materials, 1979 (Box-folder 44/31)
    - Harvard Work Study, Steve Fury - Summer 1978 (Box-folder 44/32)
    - Employment Applications, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 44/33)
    - Attorney Applicants - Rejected, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 45/1)
    - Party, 1977 (Box-folder 45/2)
    - Antioch Paralegal Program - Ercardo Lopez, 1979 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - Denise Wagner, 1979 (Box-folder 45/4)
    - Northeastern Law School - Co-op Applications & Correspondence, 1979 (Box-folder 45/5)
    - Lawyer Applications - New (post May 1977) applicants (Box-folder 45/6)
    - LELO Budget & Expenses 1975 (Box-folder 45/7)
    - LELO Budget & Expenses 1976 (Box-folder 45/8)
    - LELO Budget & Expenses 1973-1974 (Box-folder 45/9)
    - University of Washington Work Study Contract 1977-1978 School Year, 1979 (Box-folder 45/10)
    - Antioch Paralegal, 1979 (Box-folder 45/11)
    - Minority Recruiting Summer 1978, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 45/12)
    - Northeastern University Co-op Program, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 45/13)
    - Summer 1977 Law Student Hires (Box-folder 45/14)
    - LELO General Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 45/15)